Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL MY QUEEN
BY XIE LOUNAN
It's hot.
I'm fine.
You're still smiling after all this?
You care about me. That makes me happy.
Where's your medicine?
I've stopped using it.
Stopped using it?
I mean,
I don't need it anymore. I took it.
You took it,
and you're still not getting better.
I'm really fine. I just need some sleep.
You have reached Jiangzhou.
Why did you come back?
Why did you trick me into leaving?
To keep you safe.
You're the Emperor.
Your life is more important
than my safety.
Yes, I'm the Emperor,
but I'm also your husband.
Even if I can become
the Empress of the Great Qi again,
I can never be
the Ling Cangcang that Bai Chifan likes.
You haven't answered me
why you came back.
I didn't want to bear the blame
for causing your death.
But I think
you came back
because you worried about me.
I didn't.
-What are you doing?
-Stay still.
I'm cold.
Let me warm up a little.
We humbly welcome Your Majesties' arrival.
I failed in my duties,
putting both
Your Majesty and Her Majesty in danger.
Please punish me.
Xiao Huan.
Xiao Huan?
Xiao Huan!
Xiao Huan! Xiao Huan!
Guards! Summon the Imperial Preceptor.
Cangcang.
I'm here. I'm here.
Don't leave me.
I won't.
I'll always be with you.
-Your Majesty.
-Please rise. Examine His Majesty.
It's worse than I expected.
What is this?
You didn't listen to me.
To save Your Majesty as fast as possible,
His Majesty took the Yushu Pill
to force back the cold poison in his body.
But the Yushu Pill is a poison itself.
One cannot cure poison with poison.
Now that the cold poison has recurred,
his qi is obstructed throughout all organs
and both his heart and lungs
have been harmed.
Xiao Huan.
What happened? Are you all right?
-Your Majesty.
-Xiao Huan.
-Xiao Huan. What's wrong?
-Your Majesty.
Are you all right?
Your Majesty.
Don't scare me.
Are you all right?
What's happening to him?
What's wrong with him?
His condition
is extremely grave.
No. Think of something. Quick!
I told you before.
Frost Reed is the only antidote for him.
He gave it to you.
No. No.
No, I don't want it.
I don't want it.
I don't know any antidote.
Xiao Huan.
Xiao Huan!
-Xiao Huan!
-Cangcang.
-Wake up!
Look at this.
What is this?
I went to an old shaman and begged
for this medicinal bath prescription.
He once used this
to save soldiers afflicted
with cold poison.
Take a look. Will this work?
Preceptor Du.
This prescription
does have its uses.
But His Majesty's poison
has reached his lungs.
I'm not sure if…
There's no time. Hurry.
-Try it.
-Guards!
-Yes.
-Prepare a bath barrel.
Boil the medicine
according to the prescription.
Yes!
Xiao Huan.
Cangcang,
I know you've misunderstood me
many times before.
Will you give me a chance to start over?
I'll stay by your side
until the day you're willing
to walk toward me.
POST STATION
It's hot.
The fever finally broke.
Xiao Huan.
Why hasn't he woken up yet?
His heartbeat is fast.
Did the poison reach his lungs?
Xiao Huan.
Don't scare me.
Xiao Huan. Xiao Huan!
Wake up, Xiao Huan!
You can't die.
Xiao Huan. I won't blame you anymore.
I won't scold you anymore.
I won't resent you anymore.
Wake up. You can't die. Xiao Huan!
I'm not dead.
You're awake.
I'm fine.
Really?
Don't lie to me.
Even if I had died,
keeping you safe
would've been worth it.
POST STATION
You've just started to recover.
Make sure you don't catch a chill again.
All right.
Your Majesty, you're finally awake.
I suddenly feel like
eating pear blossom honey.
Great. Preceptor Du can check my pulse.
Go get it for me.
Sure.
His Majesty's poisoned veins have eased
these past few days.
Please examine him again, Preceptor Du.
Do you know
why I asked you to stay?
I don't know, Your Majesty.
Let me ask you.
When Kumor forced you
to choose between
the Phoenix Seal and the Empress,
why did you take the Phoenix Seal
and leave the Empress behind?
It was a lapse in judgment.
Please punish me.
We grew up together.
Don't lie to me.
Do you really want the truth?
Of course.
Because I think
the Empress
is a threat to you.
-Du Tingxin!
-You're the Emperor.
The entire Great Qi rests on you.
But Ling Cangcang
has dragged you into danger
again and again.
I'd rather
she never return to your side.
Do you hear yourself?
Everything I've done is for Great Qi
and for Your Majesty.
I
-have no regrets.
-Du Tingxin!
Your Majesty.
Preceptor Du,
you've completed the peace negotiation.
Leave the Phoenix Seal here
and return to the Capital at once.
I'm worried about your health.
I can't return to the Capital.
The Empress is with me.
That's enough.
Your pulse is weak.
You'll fall into longer sleeps
from now on.
Please consider your health
and allow me to stay by your side.
There are others in this world
who can treat me,
not just you.
But my empress
can only be Ling Cangcang.
Your Majesty,
you'd even throw your life away
for Ling Cangcang?
Is it worth it?
Preceptor Du, this is not your concern.
You may leave.
Your Majesty.
The grievances between
you and Her Majesty have lasted for years.
Even if you've reconciled,
how long can it really last?
Do you truly believe
that Ling Cangcang
will stay by your side
without resentment at all?
Xiao Huan, look.
Look what I brought you.
You're sleeping?
I'm just a little tired.
You're tired now?
It's late. Aren't you tired?
I'm not.
Look.
The weather in Jiangzhou is so cold
that we can make ice lanterns now.
I got a crystal lantern for you.
Is it beautiful?
It is.
I'm thinking, once you get better,
I'll take you to see ice lanterns.
How does that sound?
Great.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I was just thinking,
life here is harsher than in the palace.
Maybe
we should return to the Capital soon.
We?
You mean you and I return together?
Physician Li said
a good mood helps my condition.
What will make you happy?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
For now…
For now,
let's have a good rest.
Your pulse is weak.
You'll fall into longer sleeps
from now on.
Your Highness, we've reached Mount Xiandu.
Your Highness,
Physician Li is at the post station ahead.
Shall I go with you?
No need.
The incident in Xuzhou
must be related to Ling Xuefeng.
These guards may not all be trustworthy.
Watch them closely.
No one is allowed to leave.
Anyone who disobeys
-will be punished under military law.
-Yes, Your Highness.
Your Majesty, I'm leaving.
Won't you see me off?
From now on,
you'll be the lord governing
your own land.
Stop acting recklessly.
Before I leave,
I beg you
to give me the map of Great Qi
painted by Father.
That's something he left behind.
I want to keep it as a remembrance.
That map
records the lands, mountains, and rivers
of Great Qi.
Are you asking for it
to tell me
you still haven't given up the throne?
Bear this in mind.
As long as I'm alive,
that map will never go to you.
You may open this pouch
when the time is right.
All right. Stop trying.
It's a dead knot.
How dare you kidnap me?
Why are you tying me up?
Don't think you can act outrageously
just because His Majesty named you Regent.
Li, be honest with me.
Can His Majesty
be cured?
If he didn't know his days were numbered,
why would he give me the map?
The Frost Reed
that could save his life has been used,
but I have found a way
to replace it with Frost Blossom.
With Frost Blossom, I can keep His Majesty
safe for at least ten more years.
Really?
If I find the Frost Blossom,
Huan,
your life will be in my hands.
Frost Reed and Frost Blossom
come from the same origin,
but they grow in different places,
so their medicinal natures differ.
Still, I've found a way
to cure the cold poison
with Frost Blossom.
It favors shade and cold,
and mostly grows on cliffs.
It withers within half a day.
Bee-eaters nest in cliffside rocks.
The males often carry
Frost Blossom while courting,
dropping seeds
in their nests on the cliffs.
Someone once saw bee-eaters on
the cliffs of Mount Xiandu.
Follow the birds,
and you may find Frost Blossom.
Was Physician Li trying to fool me?
Who's that?
Well, well, Xiao Huan.
Your life is in my hands now.
Xiao Huan.
If I die here,
I'll haunt you even as a ghost.
Why is it you?
Didn't I set you free?
Why did you come back?
You spared me once,
and I'm saving you now.
We're even.
I told you to leave, and you didn't.
I've changed my mind now.
I'm not letting you go.
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
I can't just leave you on this mountain
as wolves' food.
Why did you save me?
I didn't mean to save you.
I just happened to run into you.
Why are you still denying it now?
Eat this.
This is the Blood-Replenishing Pill.
It'll help your wounds.
Where are you heading to?
I'll give you a ride.
Could it be you can't bear to leave me,
and plan to cling to me for life?
Wait.
What… What's wrong?
Why are you crying? No.
I… I didn't mean that.
I'm not saying you can't follow me.
I know you're injured,
so I was worried…
No. That's not what I meant.
Master Zhong.
Miss Zhong. Vice Sect Leader Zhong.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have stabbed you.
I shouldn't have driven you away.
It's all my fault. How about this?
Here.
You stab me too. Just not the face.
Don't ruin my beautiful face.
I don't want to!
Uh. How about this?
Hit me.
Hit my face.
Come on. Hit me.
You see,
no one has ever hit my face.
You'll be the first and only. Hit me.
Come on. Hit me.
Go on. Hit me. Hit me.
I'm crying
because the world is so big,
but I have nowhere to go.
Didn't you always talk about
wanting to see Ling Cangcang?
How would I face Cangcang?
How would I explain to her?
If you have something you can't tell her,
you can tell me.
Who are you really?
I don't want to die
without knowing the truth.
I was rescued by Master Li Lu
from the Saintess of Lingbi Sect.
After I left with him,
he only gave me one task.
No matter what happens,
protect Cangcang.
Even if it costs your life.
-Master!
-Cangcang.
Zhong Lin was an orphan
I picked up somewhere.
I kept her with us.
From now on, she'll stay by your side,
-all right?
-All right.
Don't be afraid.
I'll protect you from now on.
I never harmed Cangcang,
nor did I disobey my master.
Before Master Li Lu died,
he told me that from then on,
I only had to obey Cangcang.
I'm afraid…
You failed me.
What does this have to do
with Ling Cangcang?
I didn't even blame you.
Xiao Qianqing,
I'm sorry.
I killed you because it was
the order of Lingbi Sect's guardian.
He came after you.
If he still fails to kill you,
he won't stop.
Lingbi Sect may be divided,
but when it comes to killing,
they never leave a loose end.
So,
could you maybe shelter me for a while?
I can protect you, after all.
Forget it. You protect me?
I think it's the other way around.
Right. You protect me.
Stop pulling the long face. It's ugly.
Come on. Smile for me.
Get off. I'm being serious.
I'm going to Jiangzhou to find Xiao Huan.
I'll take you to Ling Cangcang.
If anything happens,
I'll take the blame for you.
NANRONG PALACE
Preceptor Du,
you've completed the peace negotiation.
Leave the Phoenix Seal here
and return to the Capital at once.
The Empress is with me.
That's enough.
There are others in this world
who can treat me,
not just you.
But my empress
can only be Ling Cangcang.
Madam, General Lu requests an audience.
Bring him in.
Yes, Madam.
Preceptor Du.
General Lu,
have a seat.
What brings you here?
Preceptor Du,
after I return to the Capital,
I must report to Commander Li
on my mission to Jiangzhou.
I came to ask for your guidance.
You should speak honestly in the report.
There's no need to come here
to ask about it.
Along the journey,
I had the honor
to accompany you.
I will remember what I saw and heard
for the rest of my life.
I know
you bear heavy duties
and great burdens.
It will be my honor to serve you
in any small way.
General Lu.
Yes, Madam.
Do you mean the meaning of "Nanrong"?
I do not, Madam.
"Loyal to the Divine.
If tainted by mortal desire,
Heaven and Earth will not tolerate it."
I understand now.
Then I won't disturb
your peace any further, Madam.
I'll take my leave.
Hold on.
I see by your complexion
that you're sleeping lightly
and dreaming much.
I'll have a palace maid
fetch some incense
and tonic pills for you.
You may come here
to collect them every month.
Thank you, Madam.
Madam,
restrain yourself.
Don't indulge wild thoughts.
KUMOR ARMY HAS WITHDRAWN.
JIANGZHOU WON.
I SPECIALLY SENT YOU THIS NOTE,
FATHER. CANGCANG IS SAFE AND WELL.
SHE'LL SOON RETURN WITH THE EMPEROR.
PLEASE TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, FATHER
FROM JUEDING
-Butler.
-Yes, My Lord.
Give Chongming Temple
one thousand liang for merit lamps.
Also,
give one liang of silver to every servant.
If they wish to go home,
grant them permission.
My Lord,
what has you in such high spirits?
Jiangzhou won the battle.
Jueding and Cangcang are safe.
Shouldn't we celebrate?
-Yes.
-Also,
contact the people of Jiangzhou.
Watch the two siblings closely
and report all of their movements
and every word
-they speak to the Emperor.
-Yes, My Lord.
You may leave.
Very well. Excellent.
BRUSH AND INK
My Lord,
I've failed your trust.
I couldn't kill
the Prince of Yuzhang in Xuzhou.
Please punish me,
My Lord.
Xiao Qianqing is a hard nut.
There aren't many opportunities
to kill him.
There's somewhere I need to be.
You don't have to follow me.
Stay here and think carefully
about how you fall short
of Xianxue.